Guide to the Records of The New York Institute for the Humanities RG 37.4
New York University Archives
- Series III: Audio Recordings
  - Subseries A: Cassette Tapes, 1974-2005
    - Alfred Kazin, "Writing is All: Life as a Critic", 15-Apr-94 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Nicholas Lemann, "The American Meritocracy" - master, 22-Apr-94 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Nicholas Lemann, "The American Meritocracy" - copy, 22-Apr-94 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Paul Muldoon, "A Reading of His Poetry", 29-Apr-94 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Simon Schama, 7-Oct-94 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273741
    - German House Tape 1, 14-Oct-94 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - German House Tape 1, 21-Oct-94 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Melissa Roberts, 28-Oct-94 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Fritz Stern, 18-Nov-94 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Jos Rose, 2-Dec-94 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Kurt Andersen, 9-Dec-94 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Jocelyn Carlson Baltzell, 3-Mar-95 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Jocelyn Carlson Baltzell, 10-Mar-95 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Jocelyn Carlson Baltzell, 17-Mar-95 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Jocelyn Carlson Baltzell, 31-Mar-95 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Jocelyn Carlson Baltzell, 14-Apr-95 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Jocelyn Carlson Baltzell, 21-Apr-95 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 1, 14-Jun-95 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273758
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 2, 14-Jun-95 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 3, 14-Jun-95 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 4, 14-Jun-95 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 5a, 15-Jun-95 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 5b, 15-Jun-95 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 6a, 15-Jun-95 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 6b, 15-Jun-95 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 7, 15-Jun-95 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 8a, 15-Jun-95 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 8b, 15-Jun-95 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 9, 16-Jun (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 1 copy, 14-Jun-95 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273766
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 2 copy, 14-Jun-95 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 3 copy, 14-Jun-95 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 4 copy, 14-Jun-95 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 5a copy, 15-Jun-95 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 5b copy, 15-Jun-95 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 6a copy, 15-Jun-95 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 6b copy, 15-Jun-95 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 7 copy, 15-Jun-95 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 8a copy, 15-Jun-95 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 8b copy, 15-Jun-95 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 1, 14-Jun-95 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273774
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 1 copy (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 2, 14-Jun-95 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 3, 14-Jun-95 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 4, 14-Jun-95 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 5a, 15-Jun-95 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 5b, 15-Jun-95 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 6b, 15-Jun-95 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 7, 15-Jun-95 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 8a, 15-Jun-95 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 8b, 15-Jun-95 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Michael Lind, "What is the Society for a Social Democratic Project?", 6-Oct-95 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042277817
    - Eric Hobsbawm, "Inventing Your Own History", 13-Oct-95 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Eric Hobsbawm, 13-Oct-95 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Alex Stille, "Mafia and Politics in Contemporary Italy", 20-Oct-95 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - James Atlas, "On Writing the Biography of Saul Bellow", 27-Oct-95 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Robert Wright, "Family Values in the Genes", 10-Nov-95 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Todd Gitlin, "America's Culture Wars", 3-Nov-95 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Jocelyn Carlson Baltzell, 17-Nov-95 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Jocelyn Carlson Baltzell, 1-Dec-95 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Jocelyn Carlson Baltzell, 8-Dec-95 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Sherry Turkle, 16-Feb-96 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Adrian Piper, 8-Oct-96 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Deutsches Haus, 25-Oct-96 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Vincent Crapanzano, "Conceptualizing Social and Cultural Reality Non-Textual Interpretation", 6-Dec-96 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042277825
    - Cinema Conference, nd (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Cinema Conference, nd (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Cinema Conference, nd (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Gary Wills, "The Life of St. Augustine", 26-Sep-97 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042277833
    - Richard Howard, "Ascending the Monuments: The Poetry of Homage", 3-Oct-97 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Jane Kramer, "On the Washington State Militia", 10-Oct-97 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Elizabeth Holtzman, "On the Upcoming Mayoral Election", 17-Oct-97 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - David Garland, "The New Strategies of Crime Control: Sources and Contradictions", 24-Oct-97 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Rosalind Krauss, "Painting Without a Past: Part II of Poetry Without a Past", 31-Oct-97 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Jerome Bruner, Frances Fitzgerald and Aryeh Neier - The NYIH at 20, 7-Nov-97 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - James Chace, "Dean Acheson: Faustian Bargains and the End of the Cold War", 14-Nov-97 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Andre Aciman, "Water Cities: Writing from Memory", 21-Nov-97 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Stanley Crouch, "Blues for Tomorrow", 6-Feb-98 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042277841
    - Oliver Sacks, "The End of Science", 13-Feb-98 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Brian Urquhart, "If There is a World Community, Who is the Sheriff?", 20-Feb-98 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Nancy Vickers, "Dante and the Language of Television", 27-Feb-98 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Elaine Showalter, "Hysterical Epidemics", 6-Mar-98 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Tamar Jacoby, "Integration: The Wrong Means to the Right End", 13-Mar-98 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Stanley Cavell, 27-Mar-98 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Arnold Rampersad, "The Search for the Real Jackie Robinson", 3-Apr-98 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Fareed Zakaria, "Illiberal Democracy", 17-Apr-98 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Barbara Ehrenreich, "Public Ecstasy", 24-Apr-98 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Mark Danner, "American Intervention, Haitian and Bosnian Crisis", 1-May-98 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - David Remnick, "Race, Hype, and Heavyweight Championship", 25-Sep-98 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042277858
    - Edward Said, "Opera's Problems", 2-Oct-98 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Jessica Benjamin, "Freud and Femininity", 9-Oct-98 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Catherine Stimpson, "Gertrude and Her Politics", 16-Oct-98 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Hal Foster, "The State of Criticism", 23-Oct-98 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Jane Gallop, "Resisting Reasonableness: Consensual Amorous Relations, Pedagogy, and Conflict of Interest", 30-Oct-98 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Tom Bishop, "Unblocking Memory for a Memoir", 6-Nov-98 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Jerome Bruner, "Inventing Infancy", 20-Nov-98 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Shashi Tharoor, "On India", 11-Dec-98 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Linda Nochlin, "The Modernity of Mary Cassatt", 5-Feb-99 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Rosalind Krauss, "On Jackson Pollock", 5-Feb-99 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Lawrence Weschler, "The Exile and Calamitous Return of Breyten Breytenbach", 9-Feb-99 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Ari Zolberg, "Immigration and the Future of the Nation State", 26-Feb-99 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - David Rieff, "Humanitariansim and the Human Rights: Convergence and Contradictions", 5-Mar-99 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042277866
    - Morris Dickstein, "Roots of the Counter Culture", 12-Mar-99 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Jerry Siegel, "What is Bourgeois Individualism", 9-Apr-99 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Leonard Barkan, "A Circle of Shades", 16-Apr-99 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Leonard Barkan, "A Circle of Shades", 16-Apr-99 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Robert Paxton, "Vichy in the Courtoom: The Trial of Maurice Papon", 30-Apr-99 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Particia Williams, "The Emperor's New Clothes", 30-Apr-99 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Arnold Steinhardt, "The Courtesan and the Violinist", 24-Sep-99 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042277874
    - Mary Poovey, "NYIH and Interdisciplinarity at NYU", 1-Oct-99 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Urvashi Vaid, "Toward a New Coalition in the Gay and Lesbian Movement", 15-Oct-99 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Terry Riley, "Rethinking Critical Space: Redesigning the Museum of Modern Art", 22-Oct-99 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Tony Hiss, "The View from Alger's Window", 29-Oct-99 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - David Denby, "James Agee in 1945: Movies and Criticism Now", 5-Nov-99 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Troy Duster, "The Racialization of Politics and the Politicization of Race", 12-Nov-99 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Stephen Jay Gould, "Questioning the Millennium", 19-Nov-99 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Charles Halpern, "On Y2K: Reflections at the End of the Millennium", 3-Dec-99 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Joan Acocella, "Editing Nijinsky's Diary", 10-Dec-99 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Nicholas Lemann, "Meritocracy in America", 4-Feb-00 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Richard Sennett, "Work and Its Discontents", 11-Feb-00 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Peter Singer, "The Sanctity of Life", 18-Feb-00 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Rayna Rapp, "Gender and Genomes: An Anthropological Perspective on How New Genetic Knowledge Gets Made and What Happens to It", 3-Mar-00 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Jonathan Schell, "On the Presidential Primaries", 10-Mar-00 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Mary Ellen Burns, "From Dot-dash to Dot-com: Prespectives on the Past and future of the Internet", 24-Mar-00 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Komar and Melamid, "Art and Collaboration: Other Artists, Other Species", 31-Mar-00 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Lydia Davies, On Translating Proust, 7-Apr-00 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Betty Fussell, "The Meaning of the Kitchen", 14-Apr-00 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Michael Cunningham, "Virginia Woolf and Chaos Theory: Time, Synchronicity, and Other Impossible Problems in the Novel", 22-Sep-00 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042277882
    - Doug Guthrie, "The End of History? Political, Economic and Social Change in China", 29-Sep-00 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Jessica Yu, "A Cast of Trillions: The Art of Henry Darger", 6-Oct-00 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Daniel Pipes, "The Current Crisis in the Middle East", 13-Oct-00 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Breyten Breytenbach, "Notes from the Middle World", 20-Oct-00 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Colm Toibin, "The Legacy of Coole: Lade Gregory, Sir William Gregory, and the Creation of an Irish National Identity", 27-Oct-00 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Philip Gourevitch, "Black and White and Gray Over: Some Thoughts on the Problems and Politics of Journalistic Evenhandedness", 3-Nov-00 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Robert Krulwich, "Panic in the News Room", 10-Nov-00 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Fred Siegel, "Mayors and Morality: Daley and Lindsay, Then and Now", 17-Nov-00 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Edward Rothstein, " Music and Masterpieces: Why Audiences Love the 19th Century", 1-Dec-00 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Bruce Chilton, "The Rabbi's Revenge, The Story of Jesus", 8-Dec-00 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Noelle Oxenhandler, "The Eros of Parenthood: Explorations in Light and Dark", 9-Jan-01 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Mark Salzman, "Why I Love the Bach Cello Suites: A Talk and Performance", 2-Feb-01 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Robert Hollander, "Justice and Poetry: Dante's Book of the Dead", 16-Feb-01 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Kenneth Frampton, "Megaform as Urban Landscape", 23-Feb-01 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Roald Hoffmann, "The Royal Purple and the Biblical Blue: A Story of Religion, Protochemistry and Politics", 2-Mar-01 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Michael Wood, "The Interpretation of Oracles: The Irrational and Its Reasons", 9-Mar-01 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Herbert Leibowitz, "Parnassus at 25: Some Night Thoughts of an Editor on Poets, Poetry and the Decline of Literary Language", 23-Mar-01 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Elizabeth Holtzman, "The Election and the Court", 30-Mar-01 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Martin Kace, "Coma and After", 6-Apr-01 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Claudia Roth Pierpont, "On Lincoln Kirstein", 20-Apr-01 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Francine du Plessix Gray, "Loving and Hating Simone Weil", 27-Apr-01 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Steve Reich Lunch, 23-Apr-82 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042277890
    - Bosnia, 25-Feb-93 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Denis Donohue and Gerald ?, 31-Oct-86 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Daniel Bell and Susan Sontag Tape 1, 12-Dec-94 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Daniel Bell and Susan Sontag Tape 2, 12-Dec-94 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Paul Star, 8-Feb-95 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Commercial Culture, 3-Oct-86 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Philip Glass, 30-Apr-82 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Architecture of Urban Cultural Centers, 17-Apr-79 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Public Art in the City Forum, 20-Nov-78 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Bloom, H., 14-Oct-2000 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Master 1 of 2, 13-May-2002 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Master 2 of 2, 13-May-2002 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Tony Gration on Kirchev ATC, 22-May-02 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Was A. Kirker 1 of 2, 23-May-2002 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Was A. Kirker 2 of 2, 23-May-2002 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Kapuscinski/Sacks, 18-Sept-2002 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Herbert Muschamp, 27-Sept-2002 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Fried on Adolph M Menzel 1 of 2, 14-Nov-02 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Fried on Adolph M Menzel, 15-Nov-02 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Breyten Breytenbach interviewed by Lawrence Weschler 1 of 2, 21-Nov-02 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Breyten Breytenbach interviewed by Lawrence Weschler 2 of 2, 21-Nov-02 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Mark Danner, 6-Dec-02 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Sontag/Sacks/Dyson: young and On Fire, 14-Feb-02 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Derrick Bell, 5-Sept-03 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Jorge Castaneda, 12-Sept-03 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - John Walsh on Bill Viola, 03-Oct-03 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Simon Schama, 24-Oct-03 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - NYIH Danner-Iraq, 05-Dec-03 (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - VIP Lecture Series, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Saskia Hamilton on Lowell, 28-Jan-05 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Sontag Seminar, 23-Feb-05 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Lawrence Douglas, 25-Feb-05 (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Leonard Barkam, 22-Apr-05 (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - Walter Murch, 29-Apr-05 (Box 72, Folder 25)
    - Allen Ryan, "Is Pragmatism Good for Us?", Undated (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - Michael John Gorman on Kircher, Undated (Box 72, Folder 27)
    - Elaine Scarry, "The Mothers Consent", Undated (Box 72, Folder 28)
    - Sex, Gender, Food Discussion, Undated (Box 72, Folder 29)
    - Jessica Benjamin "Return to the Oedipus Complex", Undated (Box 72, Folder 30)
    - CHCI, Undated (Box 72, Folder 31)
    - Sennett Pt 2 / Barnett Panel, Undated (Box 72, Folder 32)
    - L. Maddlebury, Undated (Box 72, Folder 33)
    - W. Houtiy Man and Machines, Undated (Box 72, Folder 34)
    - Jerome Bruner Lunch: Language and Mind, Undated (Box 72, Folder 35)
    - R. Sennett Lunch Narrative, Undated (Box 72, Folder 36)
    - Joel Meyerowitz in Conversation with Werschler reguarding Ground Zero Antecedents, undated (Box 72, Folder 37)
    - Susan Koch, Undated (Box 72, Folder 38)
    - Shabtai/Cole, Undated (Box 72, Folder 39)
    - Harvard GSD Conference: Safdie, Kollets, Sennet, Undated (Box 72, Folder 40)
    - New Rights Seminar, Undated (Box 72, Folder 41)
    - Richard Rorty, Undated (Box 72, Folder 42)
    - Biography Seminar, Undated (Box 72, Folder 43)
    - Colm, Glass, and Lynch, Undated (Box 72, Folder 44)
    - Tom Bender: Culture and the City, Undated (Box 72, Folder 45)
    - Session 1 & 2, Undated (Box 72, Folder 46)
    - Amartya Seminar, Undated (Box 72, Folder 47)
    - William Finnegan: On Donusard Mobility in America, Undated (Box 72, Folder 48)
    - Authority Conference, Undated (Box 72, Folder 49)
    - Discussion Group I, Undated (Box 72, Folder 50)
    - Thiebersohn: Lunch on Popper, Undated (Box 72, Folder 51)
    - NYIH Internal Seminar, Undated (Box 72, Folder 52)
    - R. Poirier, Undated (Box 72, Folder 53)
    - Richard Sennett Wellfleet Conference Part 3, Undated (Box 72, Folder 54)
    - Derrick Bell, Undated (Box 72, Folder 55)
    - Neil de Grasse Tyson, Undated (Box 72, Folder 56)
    - Question of Progress II, Undated (Box 72, Folder 57)
    - David Nasaw: Sex, Gender and Consumer Culture, Undated (Box 72, Folder 58)
    - Carol Vance, Undated (Box 72, Folder 59)
    - Richard Burns, Undated (Box 72, Folder 60)
    - Michael Fried, Undated (Box 72, Folder 61)
    - Richard Falk, Undated (Box 72, Folder 62)
    - Thelma Golden, Undated (Box 72, Folder 63)
    - Daniel Pinchbeck, 22-Nov-02 (Box 72, Folder 64)
    - Ryzard Kapuscinski, Undated (Box 72, Folder 65)
    - Kramer, Undated (Box 72, Folder 66)
    - Jonathan Galasci, Undated (Box 72, Folder 67)
    - David Rieff, Undated (Box 72, Folder 68)
    - David Rieff, Undated (Box 72, Folder 69)
    - Gitlin, Undated (Box 72, Folder 70)
    - Egan, Undated (Box 72, Folder 71)
    - Albie Sachs, Undated (Box 72, Folder 72)
    - Hollander, Undated (Box 72, Folder 73)
    - Bill Morrison, Undated (Box 72, Folder 74)
    - Brenda Wineapple: Hawthorne, Undated (Box 72, Folder 75)
    - Authority Conference: Session I, Undated (Box 72, Folder 76)
    - Peter Kwong, Undated (Box 72, Folder 77)
    - Anne Carson: Every Exit is an Entrance: A Praise of Sleep, 21-Feb-03 (Box 72, Folder 78)
    - Mino, Undated (Box 72, Folder 79)
    - Entifadh Qanbar, 28-Feb-03 (Box 72, Folder 80)
    - Sennett, Undated (Box 72, Folder 80)
    - Bruner, Undated (Box 72, Folder 82)
    - Walcott, Brodsky, Undated (Box 72, Folder 83)
    - Brodsky, Undated (Box 72, Folder 84)
    - Nadine Gordimer, Undated (Box 72, Folder 85)
    - D. Graham Burnett, 01-Oct-03 (Box 72, Folder 86)
    - Lukas Foss, Undated (Box 72, Folder 87)
    - G. Konrad Talk on Hungarian Literature, Undated (Box 72, Folder 88)
    - Richard Howard, Undated (Box 72, Folder 89)
    - A. Hollander: Sex, Gender and Consumer Culture - Fashion, Undated (Box 72, Folder 90)
    - A. Hollander: Sex, Gender and Consumer Culture - Fashion, Undated (Box 72, Folder 91)
    - David Harvey, Undated (Box 72, Folder 92)
    - Color, Glass, Light, Undated (Box 72, Folder 93)
    - Frances Fitzgerald: Reflections on the Irangate Hearings, Undated (Box 72, Folder 94)
    - CHCI, Undated (Box 72, Folder 95)
    - CHCI, Undated (Box 72, Folder 96)
    - Neil Harris, Undated (Box 72, Folder 97)
    - A Tribute to W.H. Auden, Undated (Box 72, Folder 98)
    - Transitions for de Tocqueville's Tapes, Undated (Box 72, Folder 99)
    - Times Square II, Undated (Box 72, Folder 100)
    - Solomon, Undated (Box 72, Folder 101)
    - William Finnegan, Undated (Box 72, Folder 102)
    - Betsy Blanchimar: Commercial Culture (Box 72, Folder 103)
    - Carol Vance, Undated (Box 72, Folder 104)
    - Costakis, Undated (Box 72, Folder 105)
    - Sam Bowles, Undated (Box 72, Folder 106)
    - Brazil Plassics, Undated (Box 72, Folder 107)
    - Breyten Breytenbach: On the South African Apartheid System (Box 72, Folder 108)
    - VIP Lecture, Undated (Box 72, Folder 109)
    - Censorship Seminar, Undated (Box 72, Folder 110)
    - Ed White, Undated (Box 72, Folder 111)
    - Martin Kace: Coma and After, 06-Apr-01 (Box 72, Folder 112)
  - Subseries B: 1/4 Inch Reels
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later I, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042277908
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later I, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later Poetry Reading I, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later Poetry Master, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later I-III, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years I-IV, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later I-V, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later II, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later II, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later II-II, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later II-III, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later II-V, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later III, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later IV, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042277916
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later Tape 4, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later CIV, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later E4, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later 5, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later Session 2 - Culture, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later Day 2 Tape 2, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later Day 2 Tape 5, 27-Sep-79-29 Sep, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - The Second Sex - Thirty Years Later Thurs. Night, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Unlabelled, undated (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Gallatin Lecture: Jane Kramer, 7-May-81 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Gallatin Lecture: Justin Kaplan -The Art of Biography, 2-Apr-81 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Future of the Intellectual Community Conference I, 11-Dec-77 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Future of the Intellectual Community II, 11-Dec-76 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - James Lecture: Wollheim "On Persons and Their Lives" I, 29-Sept-77 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - James Lecture: Wollheim "On Persons and Their Lives" II, 29-Sept-77 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - James Lecture: Wollheim "On Person and Their Lives" III, 29-Sept-77 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - James Lecture: Wollheim "On Persons and Their Lives" I, 29-Sept-77 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - James Lecture: Wollheim "On Persons and Their Lives" II, 29-Sept-77 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - James Lecture: Wollheim "On Persons and Their Lives", 29-Sept-77 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - James Lecture: Susan Sontag "Illness as a Metaphor" I Master, 13-Oct-77 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - James Lecture: Susan Sontag "Illness as a Metaphor" II Master, 13-Oct-77 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - James Lecture: Susan Sontag "Illness as a Metaphor" III Master, 13-Oct-77 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - James Lecture: Susan Sontag "Illness as a Metaphor" I Copy, 13-Oct-77 (Box 73, Folder 12)